What are we doing?
I thought the point of being here today was to have a meeting.
We are having a meeting. We're all here.
Well, yeah, but I mean, I figured you'd want to do something a little more,
I don't know, club-specific.
Are you kidding me? I got the crap ending again!
That's because no one likes you.
There's something wrong with the game!
I have to face it.
Nothing I can do will make Kageyama want to be friends with me.
You think that might be extreme?
I think there are two types of girls in this world.
There are the brilliant girls who want to be friends with me,
and then there are all those other bitches.
So, Kodaka, what were you thinking we could do?
Yeah, if you've got a suggestion, let's hear it.
Huh?
Well, how about a round-robin story?
Yeah!
Okay, what's a round robin story?
It's a story that we all get to take turns writing.
I just finished a book where the main characters wrote one together.
And it sounded like a whole lot of fun to me.
Kodaka, Rika thinks we should try it.
She's never written a normal story before.
Uh, what do you mean by normal?
Big Brother, I haven't either.
I never wrote anything!
I remember a time when I would compose various sagas every single day.
It was my sole comfort, the solace for my devastating loneliness.
Wait, are you talking about those journals you used to obsess about?
Because the only thing I ever saw in them were weird codes.
What? Those were my private thoughts, they weren't for you!
I just got a glimpse, that's all, God.
Now, I've never written one of these stories either.
But I think we write what comes naturally.
Okay.
So, how do we do this thing?
Each one of us will write a full page.
Then we pass it on to the next person,
even if we're still in the middle of a sentence.
Let's figure out the order first.
Down, down, bump!
Okay.
Yukimara, you get to go first.
Big Brother, I shall lead the attack and do you proud.
Okay, great.
Whatever you want to do.
Not me!
Big Brother was a great man, a master in the arts of both pin and sword.
He was a true warrior who sided with the weak and toppled the strong.
So bursting with charisma, he was deeply revered by even the lowliest of lowly peasants.
One day, Big Brother decided, as was his habit, to rape the villagers in a nearby town.
What?
True warriors don't rape, no rape.
And what is habit supposed to mean?
I'm not a raper.
Kodaka, why are you being so defensive about all this?
Because he feels guilty.
It's not real, it's a story.
Well, actually, it's based on real life.
Yozara told me you're in the habit of raping at least 100 girls every single day.
I thought I'd include it.
Why would you tell him that?
Why do you lie?
When he began to put on his clogs, he was shocked to discover they were warm.
Even though it was the middle of winter.
Enraged, Big Brother called for me, his official sandal bearer.
You, sandal bearer.
Admit it, you rudely sat on top of my favorite clogs.
Unprofessional.
You're wrong, sir.
I warmed them, but I did it by putting them under my kimono next to my skin.
And then Big Brother praised me with kindness I had never seen.
Your loyalty is constant and admirable.
I hope you will continue to serve me.
Of course, sir.
And so I pledged lifelong allegiance to him in the customary way.
And we all lived happily ever after.
Um, Yukimura, this is a round robin story.
You're the first writer, so you can't end it.
Oh, I apologize.
I shall flog myself immediately.
Also, you kind of just ripped off the legend about Hideyoshi being Nobunaga's sandal bearer.
I had a feeling a real man like you would know that.
Haruka, hold the phone here.
Wait, you're forgetting the elephant in the room.
Look, Yukimura took off his clothes and exposed his bare chest to you.
That's too bold, sir.
Far too bold.
Why?
Both of us are guys.
That is precisely Rika's point.
You know, I was a little embarrassed by it.
Although it's not like I would mind Big Brother seeing all of me.
Rika can't stand it!
Konaka plus Yukimura forever!
Oh, Rika's so excited her head might explode!
So then, did you do the deed with Yukimura?
No!
Why not?
Gay love is the way of the samurai!
I'm not a samurai.
I would let Kodaka do anything to me he wanted, especially if it meant that he could be a genuine samurai.
Rika is psyched now!
Rika must capture the thrill she's feeling on paper at once!
Yozura, would you mind switching turns so that Rika may experience some artistic release?
Hell no.
You're freaking me out.
Well, that's a shame.
I guess Rika will just have to fantasize wildly on her own until it's her turn.
Once upon a time, there were two boys and one was super hot at the end of Kodaka, which I went on Thursdays, and the other was totally a twink, and their love was destined to become...
All right.
I guess I'll go now.
Kodaka left home with his underling, Yukimura.
When they reached the village, they saw a girl surrounded by a group of large men.
She was in the street, totally getting raped.
The rape victim was a stupid-looking, blonde-haired, blue-eyed girl with an annoying scream, a more annoying face, and a vulgar chest that resembled cow udders.
Seriously?
You're writing that I get raped in the middle of the street?
Who said it was about you, you freaking narcissist?
Unless you see yourself as a stupid-looking, blonde-haired, blue-eyed girl with an annoying scream, an annoying face, and a vulgar chest that resembles cow udders.
I'm not stupid-looking, annoying, or vulgar, so screw you!
Oink and squeal!
I beg if you help me, even though I'm a filthy and disgusting pig.
The name of the piggy you see in front of you is Senna Kashiwazaki.
Oink and squeal!
I was right!
You just wrote my name!
You know, it's an entirely different person.
You're not like the only one in the world named Senna Kashiwazaki, okay?
This is the first time you've ever called me by my full name.
You know, that Senna may be getting raped, but this Senna is feeling pretty good.
Do you realize how twisted that sounds?
I assume by pretty good, you mean honored that I would even say a tacky name like Senna Kashiwazaki.
What?
It's not tacky.
The filthy sal named Senna Kashiwazaki begged Kotaka to rescue her, even though she knew she wasn't worth the effort.
Please save me!
Squeal, squeal!
Please rescue this loathsome porker who has the unfortunate and tacky name Senna Kashiwazaki and whose value is less than a box!
It's no use crying for help, no one wants to save Senna Kashiwazaki!
You got a big head, that's your problem!
You think you're special just cause you're rich and get good grades!
Yeah, you're really just a cheap tramp who plays porn games in the club room!
Come on, that's so mean!
It's obviously not just a look-alike with my name, it's me!
Yozara, you're being mean.
I guess he's right, I might be pushing it.
Okay, fine, I'll go ahead and write an ending for your rape scene right now.
You see, you said you're, it is me!
Don't get so caught up in the details.
At least now I'll get saved.
The leading man has to rescue me because I'm the heroine of the story.
Help this baby!
Get your stupid fun over here and rescue Senna Kashiwazaki immediately!
Sorry, I'm not into boobs that huge.
What?
It turns out Kotaka was only into little girls.
So we abandoned the swine known as Senna Kashiwazaki to search for other prey.
Kotaka, how can you just walk away like that?
I'm not the one writing this.
Yozara, why did you give me that crazy backstory about only being into little girls?
Dude, calm down, this is a work of fiction.
Yeah, well, you're still being mean.
Hm.
Whatever, it's my turn.
You mean you get to go now?
Hey, hold on!
Although I had pretended to abandon Senna, I quickly went back and single-handedly took down the bad guys.
Thank you.
You rescued me.
That's so sweet.
No problem, it was kind of weighing on my conscience, so...
According to the bad guys, their lair was a cave hidden in the west.
To create a world where the peasants could live without fear, I headed out to find the lair of the villains who kept terrorizing the town.
Naturally, I'd never had any intention of raping villagers, and the part about me only being into little girls was also a big fat lie.
The whole first part of my character development was just a strategy to deceive the enemy.
Who in the hell are you?
No one worth naming himself!
Then I completely trashed those bad guys.
That allowed the villagers to understand I was actually a very nice young man with a strong sense of justice and a heart of gold who could never forsake those in need.
You're the best hero ever!
For my other half, being the best is second nature, much like myself.
You are truly the greatest of all great men, big brother.
Well, I suppose projecting yourself onto the main character in order to take your mind off the pain of reality is a valid use for a story.
Although it's not one I would make.
Wait, hey, what does that mean?
My turn!
You all ready for brilliance?
Payback is such a bitch, right?
That was when the bad guy's disgusting and hefty leader appeared.
She was a black-haired woman with evil eyes.
A maggot-like, jealous creature who could never hope to compare with me.
Me, Yosara, me, Kazuki!
Me embody evil and full-out growth ugly!
I will slay you!
You no can!
Hey, what was that?
Flies were swarming. I had to take care of the problem.
Summer's over, but it's still hot enough for meat to go bad real fast.
Shut up! You'll pay for that!
Yosara Mikazuki's powers were pathetically weak.
Nonetheless, Kotaka quickly found himself in trouble when he fell for one of the Harpy's dirty tricks.
Wait a minute, this is a game for girls.
It was a trap!
Now let me kill you until you're dead!
Oh, no.
Is this the end for me?
Help me, gods!
Just a reminder, we are in a cave.
So what? That kind of thing doesn't matter!
And lo and behold, the goddess that appeared was none other than the sublimely perfect and beautiful Sina Kashiwazaki.
As you can obviously tell, I am a goddess.
I allowed myself to be assaulted by those villains in order to test the human race.
In reality, I could have easily wiped those scumbags from the face of the earth.
Now, evildoer, you shall be gone!
Ow! Will you stop doing that?
Oink!
I want you to beg for your life on bended knee, right now. If you do, I shall spare you.
O great and beautiful Sina, me never knew bad things again!
Please no kill Yozora, let live me!
Fine. If you truly wish to be forgiven, you may lick my foot.
Be so thankful for gorgeous goddess, his mercy!
The hideous Yozora dutifully licked my foot with no sign of embarrassment.
Kodika thanked the goddess as well.
So I stepped on his head as a reward for his faithfulness.
At the time, his face practically glowed with ecstasy.
Please allow me to lick your foot!
He beseeched me.
I was kind enough to take off my sandal and put my foot in his mouth.
You perp!
You lost your mind!
Oink, stop! What's your problem?
I spared your life and allowed you to lick my foot.
You should be grateful.
You seriously think I should be grateful to lick someone's nasty foot and beg for my life?
I've never, ever been this humiliated before.
Oh, please! Like, you can talk! You had me get raped!
Apologize to me, meat.
Okay, fine. Sorry.
Guess I went a little too far, too.
Now, why don't you act like you mean it?
What are you?
What's that?
You know, right?
I mean, you are the one who wrote about how people should show they're truly sincere.
There's no way!
I won't!
I don't lick shoes.
Even if I liked that kind of thing, I'd still never kiss your shoe!
I hate you, Yozara! You're so stupidly stupid!
So, do we keep going?
Why not? Her turn's over.
I say, roll with it.
C-c-c-c-
Prepare yourselves, for I shall now allow you fools to glimpse my torrent of intellectuality.
I forgot she's next!
I wouldn't miss this one for the world!
Go on, show them how it's done, Kobito!
There's something majorly wrong with you.
Never mind her! Get on with the story!
My soul's other half, losing himself in the creepy goddess's enticement,
moved in to kiss her stinky foot, when suddenly...
Awaken, blood of darkness!
Remember yourself, Roga Vilhelm Zaylis!
Um, where did the goddess I was playing go?
More importantly, who's this Roga guy?
Please don't tell me you've forgotten that.
Roga is your rightful name.
However many times you may be reborn,
it shall always be your true name,
branded unchanging upon your very soul.
Okay, please don't tell me I also sparkle in the sunlight.
Say that again, and I'll kill you myself!
This light, I've seen it before!
Oh, wow!
It's RACIS!
The painful, yet beloved memory
sprang back to life in his mind.
RACIS and Roga's first chance encounter
dates back to the 13th century.
This doesn't seem unrealistic to you.
C-c-c!
Too real for your human blood.
You will never understand the thrill
that comes from two souls resonating.
The name of that girl with the mismatched eyes
was RACIS V Felicity Sumeragi.
She of the Night Tribe,
and he of the Daylight Clan.
Their love was forbidden,
and it would end in tragedy.
Awkwardness makes my back itchy.
Aw!
Your brother Complex is adorable as ever!
You're so messed up!
C-c-c!
This page is now touched with immortality.
The thousand-page tale of our cycle of reincarnation
shall be told.
Maybe you should save that for your private notebook.
Out of the way!
I'm next!
Take care,
oh foolish minion of God.
You shall pin the next chapter of my saga,
so tread carefully or you shall pay.
No way!
Your story is stupid and boring.
What?
So I think I'm gonna go with something else.
Hey, you're stupid and boring.
Oh no!
Look at what I have done!
I went and have stepped in poo.
You're way dirty now!
Ew!
You're stinky gross!
I know why this tragedy has fallen on me.
It's because I am a stupid, stinky vampire
who is bad and evil.
You are right about that.
If you had God's protection,
you for sure wouldn't be covered in poo right now.
I think we should go to church together
and receive God's blessing.
Yes, let's go to church.
Oh, she turned into ashes?
Oh, she turned into ashes.
What?
It is.
I am a stupid, stinky vampire
who is bad and evil.
who is evil.
You are right about that.
If you had God's protection,
you for sure wouldn't be covered in poo right now.
I think we should go to church together
and receive God's blessing.
Yes, let's go to church.
Oh, she turned into ashes.
ashes you need not mourn her death the evil vampire has been called to heaven
and shall be evil no more how wonderful so um this story is about what happens
if you accidentally crap yourself
finally behold rika shall end this story with a surprising twist are you
planning to twist in a plot just leave it to rika hold on to your hat
driven to despair by memories of his previous life kotaka awoke to the powers of darkness
destroyed god and then sought to annihilate the earth itself what for because of memories of his
previous life oh the point he's awakened to his powers of darkness the only one who could stop
kotaka was his ever faithful servant ukimura soothe away your sorrow with every part
of my being ukimura took the opportunity during that moment of hesitation to rip off kotaka's armor
abandoning his own external defenses in the process reacting to his elegant naked form kotaka's gt drive
activated i'm activating
kotaka's hard shaft rolled proudly up towards the heavens and without hesitation ukimura boldly took
the tool into his mouth a groan resembling that of a caterpillar belt on a tank escaped kotaka's mouth
with obscene sounds like when the neo's army mechanics do an energy reveal of the argi
ukimura's tongue like a foul heat whip made an incessant onslaught on kotaka's particle beam cannon
kotaka was taken aback by this oral offense
and before long spilled his lust into yukimura's skilled mouth with a passion reminiscent of mazangai zi's breast flare
kotaka released a sorrowful yet seductive breath like the gum disexia after holandzam ends
yes though kotaka's giga bazooka had fired only moments ago it showed no signs of slowing down
kotaka roughly inserted his eager mega drill into yukimura's rear coupling unit a la guzan ramen
penetrated from behind yukimura gave a squeal akin to a mondarian hit with sao daigar's broken magnum
and quickly achieved release they continued to seek pleasure in each other for the entire night
the end
i have to admit that climax is rather salacious even for rika well rika needs to have a moment at
her desk if you'll excuse her hold on just a minute yes how can i help you wait are you offering to
assist rika and giving her a moment come on rika i stopped you because this story doesn't make any
sense how does that end anything what are you talking about it's everything a happy ending should be
in what way boy love as long as before the very end the couple gets to have sex the reader will still
feel as though the story hung together even if the plot didn't make sense and there was no resolution
erotic video games work a lot like that too
you know it's also the same thing in the real world as long as you've got love it's a happy ending
i'll bite what's the real world this we're in it i wonder when we find out what happens in kotaka's story
if he'll get to find love and have a happy ending stop hey will you knock it off please
love
yeah
so lame
it's okay big brother i love you so you can marry me
no let go of him dummy
don't have me dummies stinky poopy vampires don't have the right to touch me so back up
you need to leave my brother alone right now
shut up
no you shut up no you shut up
all right that's enough
yeah so anyway before we get to love and anybody's happy ending we probably ought to focus on making
some friends first
yeah true enough
friends right
well that concludes today's activities let's work hard again tomorrow
you know at our club's mission let's all go make some friends